NCIS新奥尔良 S03E16
不用了 谢谢 Hoyt
No, thanks, Hoyt.
明天还要上班 已经很晚了
School night, it's getting late.
不是我给你的
Not my idea.
是她
It's hers.
看得出来 她是你的粉丝
Apparently, you got a fan.
已经看你弹琴好久了
Been watching you play for a while now.
你想让我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
我来处理吧
I'll handle it.
谢谢你请我喝酒
Thanks for the drink.
觉得你需要它
Thought you could use it.
是吗 为什么呢
Really? Why's that?
哦 好像有点紧绷
Oh, seem a little tense.
你也许需要弹得放松一点
You might want to lighten up on the keys.
哦
Oh.
音乐评论家啊
Music critic, huh?
你也弹钢琴吗
You play?
没有 不过我以前偶尔会唱歌
No. I used to sing a little, though.
很久以前了
Long time ago.
为什么不唱了呢
Why'd you stop?
为我弹钢琴的人走了
Lost my piano player.
顺便告诉你 我现在还没有原谅你
By the way, I still haven't forgiven you.
声明一下
For the record...
不干了的可不止我一个
wasn't just me who ended it.
再说 25年了还记仇 也太久了
Besides, 25 years is a long time to hold a grudge.
26年 可谁在意呢
26, but who's counting?
我听说你搬回来了
I heard you moved back.
我还在想 我们什么时候会偶遇呢
I wondered when we'd bump into each other.
我忘了这个城市发生的一切
Forgot nothing happens in this town
都逃不过你的眼
without you knowing about it.
没错
Yeah.
你看起来很不错 Dwayne
You look good, Dwayne.
你也是 Rita
You, too, Rita.
对了
By the way,
你和Lloyd的事我很遗憾
sorry to hear about you and Lloyd.
你和Linda的事我也很遗憾
Sorry to hear about you and Linda.
离婚真烦 对吧
Divorce sucks, right?
是啊
Yeah.
♪ Sometimes you gotta just move on... ♪
别误会 我是非常高兴见到你的
Don't get me wrong, I'm, uh, I'm glad to see you and all,
但是 时隔这么多年
but, uh... buying me a drink at 1:00 in the morning
只是在凌晨1点给我买酒么
after all these years?
一切还好吗
Everything all right?
不
No.
不好
No, it's not.
♪ No one else gonna love you like I do. ♪
就是这样
That's it,
我得换个交通工具
I got to find a new mode of transportation.
别误会 我是一个完完全全的小摩托男
I mean, don't get me wrong, I'm a moped guy through and through.
但我不喜欢物理定律
But the law of physics is not in my favor
当一辆巨大的SUV直接驶到我的...
when there's a huge SUV riding right up my...
-玻璃杯 -是和"玻璃"押韵
- Glass. - Well, yeah, rhymes with “glass”"
但那不是我要说的
but that's not what I was gonna say it was.
不不不 我是说
No, no, no. I mean...
这个玻璃杯
this glass.
过来看
Check it out.
这不会又是整蛊新人的玩意吧
This isn't another newbie hazing thing?
过来看看嘛 求你 行吗
Just look at it, please, will you?
你发现了什么
What do you see?
口红印
Lipstick.
看来昨晚Pride和某人在这里
Looks like Pride had some company over here last night.
和某位女士
Female company.
哦 你是说
Oh, you mean...
Pride吗 工作场所陪女人
Pride? Lady time at work?
不 我不这么认为
Nah, I don't think so.
嘿 咖啡好了吗
Hey, is coffee on?
嘿 Lasalle 明天
Hey, Lasalle, tomorrow,
你能顺路来接我吗
do you think you can swing by and pick me up, too?
-我不想骑我的小摩托了 -不好意思
- I'm done with my moped, man. - Excuse me.
你就直接忽略这个了吗
Are you just gonna ignore this?
忽略什么
Ignore what?
Gregorio觉得Pride
Well, Gregorio seems to think
昨晚有个约会
that Pride had a date last night.
没错
Yes.
深夜 亲自做的晚餐 喝点酒
Late night, home-cooked meal, couple of drinks,
口红印 有在听吗
lipstick? Hello.
这闻着都不像酒
Doesn't even smell like alcohol.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
你们最起码不应该觉得好奇吗
Aren't you guys the least bit curious about this?
不 因为不管这里发生了什么 绝对不是你想的那样
No, 'cause whatever “this” is, it's not what you think.
King不是那种人
Our King's not like that.
他不会把任何人带到办公室来
He wouldn't bring anybody to the office.
不是哪种人 他就住在楼上
Like what? He lives upstairs.
你才刚来 Gregorio 所以你不了解
You're still new, Gregorio, so you don't know.
-你不了解 -你不了解
- You don't know. - You don't know.
我们知道的是
What we've learned
Pride和他的工作结婚了
is Pride is married to his work.
句号
Period.
好吧
Okay.
All right.
赌20块我是对的
$20 says I'm right.
没问题
You're on.
我们有案子了
Got a case.
美国海军执法署律师 Noah Sandler
JAG lawyer Noah Sandler.
Judge Advocate General(美国海军执法署)
为海军诉讼高级机密案件
Prosecutes highly classified cases for the Navy.
他失踪了
He's gone missing.
失踪多久了
For how long?
最后一次和人联系
The last time anybody heard from him
是前天晚上
was the night before last.
他给执法署的同事打了个电话
Called a fellow JAG.
说自己有敏感事务要和她讨论
Said he had something sensitive to discuss with her,
但一直没出现
but never showed.
她
Her?
预备役Devereaux律师 也是个检察官
Reserve JAG Devereaux, also an A.D.A.
她是Noah的老师
She trained Noah.
带他入行 知道如果不是重要的事
Gave him his start. Knows he wouldn't have called
他不会给她打电话的
if it wasn't important.
所以她认为他出事了
So she thinks something happened to him?
对 我们都这么认为
Yeah, we both do.
-Rita和我去了他的... -Rita
- Rita and I went to his... - Rita?
抱歉
Sorry.
Devereaux律师和我
JAG Devereaux and I
昨晚去了他的公寓
went to his apartment last night,
但没有他或者他的车的踪迹
but there were no signs of him or his car.
尽管如此 这才过了一天半
Well, still, it's only been a day and a half.
警局对失踪人口立案需要
I mean, NOPD doesn't even take missing persons cases
48小时
for what, 48 hours?
对 但我们不是警局
Yeah, well, we're not NOPD.
我们现在说的这个也不是一般人
And this isn't just anybody we're talking about here.
抱歉 我
Sorry. Look, I...
我承认一切都看起来没什么特别
I admit there's nothing much to go on here yet,
但我认识Rita很久了
but I've known Rita a long time.
她不是容易慌张的人
She's not one to panic easily.
她很担心
She's concerned.
我跟她说了 我们会帮忙
I told her we'd help.
你的朋友就是我们的朋友 King
A friend of yours is a friend of ours, King.
下一步我们怎么做
What's our next move?
我们在Noah律师的公寓发现的唯一疑点是
Only thing suspicious we found at JAG Noah's apartment
他的电脑上什么都没有
was there was nothing on his computer.
什么都没有 就像是被清除了吗
Nothing? Like it had been erased?
对 我想让你和Patton去处理它
Yeah. I want you and Patton to work on it.
也许你们能恢复原有的文件
Maybe see if you can restore what was on it.
可以给我们一些线索
Might give us some leads.
Christopher Percy 详查Noah
Christopher, Percy, deep dive Noah.
信用卡记录 通话记录
Credit card charges, phone records,
监控录像
surveillance cameras.
任何能提供
Anything that might help us trace
他最后出现地点的线索
his last known whereabouts.
没问题
You got it.
我做什么
What can I do?
你和我
You and I
去[路易斯安那]Belle Chasse
are going to Belle Chasse.
好
Okay.
看看 Noah的哪起案子和他的失踪有关系
See if we can figure out which, if any, of Noah's cases
如果有的话
have something to do with his disappearance.
机密案件 我们有权限吗
Classified cases-- do we have access?
有 并且Rita会去跟我们会合
Yeah, we do, and Rita will meet us there
帮我们解决问题
to help us sort things out.
那好
Okay, then.
我很期待和这个Rita会面
Look forward to meeting this Rita.
不要误会我
Don't get me wrong.
要说我来这里后 懂得了什么
If there's anything I've learned since I got here,
那就是你有特定的司法方式
is you have a definite nose for justice.
就是 用很不平常的方式接案子
It's just, you know, unusual way of taking the case, is all.
你想说什么 Gregorio
What are you trying to get at, Gregorio?
没什么 我只是说
No, nothing. I'm just saying,
我们通常是有了案子才开始行动
we usually start things off with an actual crime.
接到来电 有尸体
Phone call, a body.
但现在 很大程度是依赖于你的这个朋友Rita
But here, banking a lot on this Rita friend of yours.
你一定有很充分的理由来相信她的直觉吧
You must have good reason to trust her instincts.
确实是
I do.
哦
Oh.
继续试探 纽约官
Keep fishing, New York.
谢谢你来 Dwayne
Thanks for doing this, Dwayne.
不用谢
No thanks necessary.
特别探员Tammy Gregorio
Special Agent Tammy Gregorio,
地方助理检察官 预备役海军中校
Assistant District Attorney, Reserve Naval Commander,
执法署警官 Rita Devereaux
JAG Corps Rita Devereaux.
很多头衔 我知道
Lot of titles, I know.
你可以叫我Rita
You can call me Rita.
很高兴见到你 Rita
Nice to meet you, Rita.
地方法院同意我们介入么
D.A. get us any access?
必须回到现役才能拿到 但是可以
Had to go back on active duty to get it, but yes.
幸亏制服还合身 有一段时间没穿了
Glad the uniform still fits. It's been a while.
不 你看起来棒极了
No, you look great.
-谢谢 -嗯
- Thank you. - Yeah.
女士们
Ladies? Yeah.
我们在Noah的卷宗里有发现任何有帮助的线索么
We find anything in Noah's case files that might help?
很可惜 还是毫无线索
No, nothing yet, unfortunately.
我找遍了他手头上的所有待处理案件
I've gone through all his current JAG caseload,
尽管很敏感
but although sensitive,
但没有发现什么疑点
nothing stands out as suspicious.
他的电脑呢 也被清空了么
What about his computer? Has that been erased, too?
没有 电脑看起来保存完好
No, it seems to be intact.
最后一次上机是在
His last entry was calendaring the meet
安排和我明早的行程
he wanted to have with me tomorrow morning.
家里的电脑被清空了 办公室的却没有
Home computer wiped, office not?
如果Noah真的失踪了
If Noah's really missing,
更有可能是因为私人原因而非工作原因
could be more of a personal nature than business.
Gregorio说的对
Gregorio's right.
如果这里没有任何线索
If there aren't any leads here,
而他的公寓却有...
but there were at his apartment...
你很了解他
Look, you knew him well.
他下班之余都会干些什么
What did he do with his personal time?
我几个月前才刚搬回来
We really haven't had a chance to catch up
我们真没什么机会见面
since I moved back here a couple months ago.
哦 你在新奥尔良住过么
Oh, you lived in New Orleans?
很久以前了 那还是
Long time ago, way, way back
我第一次遇到Dwayne的时候
when I first met Dwayne.
Noah似乎和Fort MacArthur有很深的关联
Looks like Noah was pretty involved with Fort MacArthur.
Fort MacArthur是什么
What's Fort MacArthur?
城外一家私人军事院校
Private military academy outside the city.
那座学校在城里有很长的历史了
Town has a long-standing history with the school.
接收有犯罪前科的问题少年
Takes in troubled juvies with criminal records.
那里是他们回头是岸的最后机会
Place is their last shot at turning their lives around.
对Noah来说就是这样
Just like it did for Noah.
学校给他提供了教育和指导
Academy offered him structure and direction.
这就是他参加海军的原因
It's why he joined the Navy.
也是他一直在那里做志愿者的原因
And why he's been volunteering there ever since.
他想要报答
He likes to give back.
其实 和你很像
A lot like you, actually.
看起来你的朋友
Looks like your friend
不只是在做志愿者
was doing more than volunteering.
学生档案 记录本
Student files, log books,
休假申请
leave requests,
学校土地的工程图纸
blueprints of the school's ground.
我觉得 这更像是
I mean, it almost feels like
他在那里调查某些东西
he was investigating something there.
我很好奇是什么
I wonder what.
你有什么线索 Sebastian
What you got, Sebastian?
好
Okay.
我们这就来 告诉Christopher
We're on our way. Uh, tell Christopher
我们去那儿跟他们会合
we'll meet them there.
Noah的电脑是被远程清除的
Noah's computer was erased remotely,
但是他们可以通过IP地址追踪到他的手提电脑
but they were able to trace the IP address to his laptop.
打给我 无论好坏
Call me. Good or bad.
一定
Promise.
Noah Sandler的车
Noah Sandler's vehicle.
从车胎印看 它停在这儿一整夜了
Judging by the tire tracks, it sat here overnight.
-有发现Noah么 -暂时没有
- Any sign of Noah? - Not yet.
知道他一直待在这儿干什么吗
Any idea what he was doing all the way out here?
可能是猎捕短吻鳄
Well, it could have been gator hunt.
有装备
Got the gear.
这是一个好地方 但是要够胆量
It's a popular spot, but you got to have courage.
什么意思
Meaning?
伊利湖并不是捕猎的安全地方
Lake Verret's not the safest place to hunt.
非常偏僻 并且危险
It's pretty remote and dangerous.
一般没有人会独自过来
Nobody usually comes out here alone.
手提电脑找到了 但是也被清除干净了
Found the laptop, but it's been wiped clean, too.
据Sebastian说
And according to Sebastian,
它曾被用来远程清除Noah家里的电脑
it was used to remotely erase Noah's home computer first.
Noah并不是大老远过来清除电脑的
Noah didn't come all the way out here to erase computers.
King
King.
哇哦
Whoa.
走开
Hyah. Get back. Hyah.
Hyah. Get back.
走开
Get back.
去 去
Hyah. Yeah.
走开
Get back.
去
Hyah.
这应该是Noah
It's probably Noah.
看起来 他中了两枪
Looks like he's been shot twice.
也就是说 失踪人员案现在变成谋杀案了
Which means our missing persons case just turned into a murder.
Wade医生给你打电话了么
Hey, Doc Wade call you yet?
没有 怎么
No, why?
她刚刚给Noah律师做了初步尸检
She just finished her prelim autopsy on JAG Noah.
结果证明你是对的
Turns out you were right.
他被人从后面开了两枪
He was shot twice in the back.
是捕猎意外么
Hunting accident?
我不觉得 创口离得很近
I don't think so. It was a tight pattern,
而且两枪都是直击心脏
and both went right through the heart.
致命枪杀
Kill shots.
问题是 谁杀了他 为什么杀他
Question is, who killed him and why?
看起来 他是自己开车出去的
Looked like he drove out there by himself.
有人在守株待兔
Someone lying in wait,
想让这看起来是捕猎时出现的意外
hoping to make it look like a hunting accident?
他们怎么知道他会去那里呢
Yeah, how'd they know he'd even be out there?
他又为什么去呢
And why was he there?
给你的朋友Rita打电话
Calls your friend Rita,
说他想和她谈一个敏感的案子
says he wants to discuss a sensitive case with her.
所以 这肯定跟
Well, it had to be connected to whatever case
他想和她谈的案子有关 是么
he wanted to talk to her about, right?
而且告诉她 这很重要
And told her it was important.
现在的情况是 如果Rita没有来找我
Thing is, if Rita hadn't come to me when she did,
我们可能永远都找不到Noah的尸体
probably never would have found Noah's body.
鳄鱼会把尸体吃光的
Gators would have made sure of that.
凶手想要的是什么呢
Was probably what the killer was hoping for.
你和Patton有没有查出
You and Patton have any luck figuring out
Noah的电脑被清除前有什么东西
what was on Noah's computers before they got erased?
没有 我们甚至黑进云端去检查数据流
Nada. We even hacked into the cloud to check the data stream.
也就是说 不管这个人是谁
Which means whoever it was
都花了很大的功夫
went through an awful lot of trouble
来掩盖Noah正在查的事情
to cover up whatever Noah was working on.
有消息吗
Any word?
你说你会打电话的
You said you would call.
我知道 但我们刚回来
I know. But we just got back,
而且我 想先确定一件事
and I... I wanted to be sure first.
确定什么
Sure of what?
不论结果好坏 你都想知道
Good or bad, you wanted to know.
这不是件好事
It's not good.
Noah被杀了 Rita
Noah was murdered, Rita.
被枪杀了
He was shot.
什么
What?
怎么会 谁干的
How? Who?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们刚开始调查
We just started the investigation.
我猜
I assume that...
你有一直在查
that you've kept looking.
知道Noah想要和你说的是什么吗
Any idea what Noah wanted to talk to you about yet?
什么事那么重要
What was so important?
我 呃
I, uh...
我认为和Terrence Lewis有关
I think it had something to do with Terrence Lewis.
他是Noah在学校
He's one of the cadets
指导的军校学员之一
that Noah was mentoring at the academy.
我在你离开后
I started looking more
开始进一步查找Noah和Fort MacAArthur的联系
into Noah's Fort MacArthur connections after you left.
Lewis有什么特别的吗
What's so special about Lewis?
Noah要求看
Uh, Noah had requested
那个男孩的少年犯档案
the boy's juvenile criminal file,
但是没有法庭命令 执法署不能接触
but JAGs can't access a minor's record
未成年人档案
without a court order.
但是地方检察官可以 你认为
But A.D.A.s can, and you're thinking that, uh,
他打电话给你 是希望你能给他文件
he called you, hoping you could get him the files?
Terrence Lewis是坏孩子
Troubled kid, Terrence Lewis.
袭击 持械抢劫
Assault, armed robbery,
他在学校也没有重新做人
and it doesn't look like he got reformed at the academy, either.
还是在学校内外
Kept getting into trouble,
不断惹麻烦
both in and out of Fort MacArthur.
如果Terrence Lewis知道Noah在调查他
If Terrence Lewis knew Noah was investigating him...
他可能杀了他 是吗
He might have killed him so he couldn't?
这是延伸的猜测
That's a stretch.
我只是在寻找真相 Dwayne
I'm just looking at the facts, Dwayne.
这是我的工作
It's what I do.
很抱歉 但不是每个孩子都会被改变的
And I'm sorry, but not every kid can be reformed.
Lewis看起来就没有
And Lewis looks like he wasn't.
暴力背景 持有武器
Violent background, access to weapons,
接着是 Noah在我们见面前被枪杀
and then Noah gets shot to death before we can even meet?
如果那不是可能的原因 我不知道还有什么了
If that's not probable cause, I don't know what is.
别急着判断
Don't want to rush to judgment here.
特别是关系到学校里的孩子
Especially when it comes to the kids at the academy.
嫌疑人就是嫌疑人 与年龄无关
Suspects are suspects, regardless of age.
听着 我知道Noah是你的朋友
Look, I know that Noah was your friend.
跟这个没有关系
That's got nothing to do with this.
有关系 你无法理智思考
It does when you're not thinking straight
因为你很生气
'cause you're loaded for bear.
可能是我第一次争赢了你
Might be the first argument I ever won with you.
我有很好的团队 Rita
I got a good team here, Rita.
他们工作做得很好
They're good at their jobs.
让我们去调查Terrence Lewis
Let us investigate Terrence Lewis
不管这事
and whatever connection
跟学校有没有关系
the academy may or may not have had in this,
我保证 我们会找出杀害Noah的凶手
and I promise we'll find out who killed Noah.
好吧
Okay.
但如果你们没找到 我会的
But if you don't, I will.
Pride探员吗 我是Walsh上将
Agent Pride? General Walsh.
对你早有耳闻 很高兴终于见到你了
Heard a lot about you. It's nice to finally meet you.
你也是 将军
You, too, General.
特别探员Percy和Lasalle
Special Agents Percy and Lasalle.
-欢迎 -你好 将军
- Welcome. - Hey, General.
-欢迎 -谢谢
- Welcome. - Thank you.
立正
Atten-hut.
所以
So...
NCIS怎么会来Fort MacArthur
what brings NCIS to Fort MacArthur?
最好在私下里谈
Well, probably best to discuss in private.
孩子们在这儿
Minors around,
我们想尽可能保持低调
want to handle this as sensitively as possible.
明白 感谢你们
Understood... and appreciated.
尤其是考虑到大多数学员的来历
Especially considering where most of our cadets come from.
警察往往把他们想得很坏
Law tends to assume the worst about them.
Sklahr将军 那是谁
Uh, General Sklahr, who is that?
他是创建这个地方的人
He was the man who practically founded this place.
你认识吗
You're familiar?
在这个城市长大的人很难不知道
Hard to grow up in this town and not be.
他做了很多好事 帮助了很多问题少年
All the good he did, troubled kids he helped.
给了他们一个家 第二次机会
He gave 'em a home, a second chance.
Sklahr将军对大多数孩子来说
General Sklahr was the father figure
是不曾有过的父亲的形象
most of these boys didn't have.
很难接替的角色
That's large shoes to fill.
被任命从事这样的工作感到很自豪
Proud to have been appointed to do exactly that.
但是 说比做要容易
Although, easier said than done.
停
Halt!
♪ The military live... ♪
说吧 孩子们惹上什么麻烦了
So, which of my boys is in trouble?
暂时还不确定
Well, not sure any are yet.
所以我们才来到这儿
That's why we're here.
希望得到协助
Hoping for an assist.
我们想和一个学员谈一谈 Terrence Lewis
We'd like to talk with one of your cadets, Terrence Lewis.
我也想
Well, so would I.
Lewis士兵已经擅自缺勤三周了
Private Lewis has been UA for three weeks now.
但我说不上这不正常
Wish I could say that was unusual.
Lewis经常失踪吗
Lewis go missing often?
很遗憾 是的
Unfortunately, yes.
我们很自豪能在这里改造孩子
We take pride here in reforming boys,
教他们遵守规矩
teaching 'em to obey orders,
如何面对比自身强大的东西
how to commit to something larger than themselves.
但是 我们并不总能成功
But, we're not always successful
恐怕Lewis士兵就是这一类
and I'm afraid that includes Private Lewis.
你通知警局他失踪了吗
You notify NOPD he was missing?
他们人手不足
They don't have the manpower
无法追踪逃跑者 而且...
to chase down runaways and...
像Lewis这样的孩子没有优先级
juvies like Lewis aren't a high priority.
他做了什么
What's he done?
重申一遍 我们不确定 但是
Again, not sure, but, uh...
很抱歉这么说
I'm sorry to say,
Noah Sandler律师被杀害了
JAG Noah Sandler has been murdered.
Terrence Lewis是嫌犯之一
And Terrence Lewis is a person of interest.
Noah 天啊
Noah, my God.
怎么回事 什么时候
How, when?
昨晚
Last night.
我们现在知道的是 Noah在调查Lewis
And what we know now is: Noah was investigating Lewis.
也许还调查这个学校
And maybe even the academy.
调查
Investigating?
Noah从来没和我说过
Noah never said anything to me about it
他一直在这里
and he was here all the time.
他教导许多孩子 不只有Lewis士兵
He mentored lots of boys, not just Private Lewis.
我们可以和Lewis的指挥官谈一谈吗
Is it all right if we speak with Lewis' commanding officer?
当然
Of course. Uh...
Dorsey 请进来
Dorsey, come in here, please.
长官
Sir?
这些是NCIS的探员们 Dorsey上校
These are NCIS agents, Captain Dorsey.
他们要和Carbral少校谈话 越快越好
They need to speak to Commander Cabral ASAP.
好的 长官 这边请
Yes, sir. Right this way.
Pride探员
Agent Pride?
Noah去世的消息会严重打击到孩子们
This news of Noah's death is gonna hit the boys hard.
我希望由我来告诉他们 如果可以的话
I'd rather they hear it from me, if that's all right with you.
好的
Yes, sir.
有什么发现 Loretta
What do we got, Loretta?
抱歉 这个问法太像Pride了
I'm sorry, that was way too much like Pride.
那太糟糕了 我得改一改
That was awful. God, I got to work on that.
我会改的 会好的
I'll work on it, it's gonna be fine.
别用力过猛 Sebastian 你做得不错
Stop trying so hard, Sebastian, you're doing fine.
我知道 我知道 我知道 只是
I know, I know, I know, it's just...
我大概还在找自己在NCIS的风格
still trying to find my NCIS way, I guess. You know?
也许我应该继续做个闷罐子
Maybe I should keep the moped.
你是来问进展的吧
You here for an update?
没错 好几颗求知的心想要知道进展
I am. Yeah, inquiring minds want to know.
尤其是Pride
Especially Pride's.
显然 一个完整的尸体会有帮助
Well, obviously, an intact body would have helped,
但是从可见的割伤和磨损的痕迹
but from the pattern of the cuts and abrasions I've seen,
以及没有凝血作用来看
coupled with the lack of coagulation,
Noah律师的尸体是在死后被拖过去的
it appears JAG Noah's body was dragged postmortem.
因为嘀嗒嘀嗒的鳄鱼么
Because of Tick-Tock Croc?
这是《彼得潘》里面的
It's a Peter Pan reference.
不管怎么说
Anyway,
短吻鳄的咬痕
the alligator bite pattern didn't match
跟割痕的方向并不一致 所以
the indicated direction of the cuts, so...
凶手一定是射杀Noah以后 才把他拖走的
So the killer must have dragged Noah after he shot him,
拖到离水更近的地方
closer to the water.
指望着短吻鳄能吃掉证据
Hoping the alligators would devour the evidence, yes.
不过对我们确认凶手身份
Doesn't really get us any closer
没什么很大的帮助
to IDing the killer, though.
我们有没有什么办法
Is there any way that we can, uh,
能缩小枪支范围的
narrow down what type of gun was used?
这肯定是某种自动步枪
It was definitely an automatic rifle of some kind.
根据
Based on the...
入射伤口来看 可能是军用枪支
entry wound, probably military.
在你找到子弹之前 我没法确定
I can't be sure until you find me the projectiles.
是啊 这就得看运气了 对吧
Yeah, well, good luck with that, right?
一个威力强大的步枪 子弹穿过人体
A high-powered rifle, bullets went right through the body,
可能被埋在小河附近的什么地方
it's probably buried back in the bayou somewhere.
嗯 在我听来像是需要一次外勤行动
Mm-hmm. Sounds like a field trip to me.
没错
Yeah.
等等 你是说我吗
Wait, do you mean me?
你想让我回到那个
You-- you want me to go back out there
致命的短吻鳄的世界 我一个人
to deadly gator-world? By myself?
嘀嗒嘀嗒的鳄鱼
Tick-Tock Croc.
好吧
All right.
我不会再见到你了
I'll see you never.
全体注意 立正
Platoon, atten-hut!
下午好 长官
Good afternoon, sir.
稍息 少校
At ease, Commander.
Cabral少校 这些是NCIS探员
Commander Cabral, these are NCIS agents.
他们需要跟你单独说几句话
They need to speak with you in private.
好的 长官
Of course, sir.
Cole 出列
Cole, front and center.
你来指挥 上尉
Your command, Lieutenant.
是 长官
Aye, sir.
我还是不能理解
Still can't wrap my head around
教少年犯用M16步枪射击
how teaching juvies to shoot M16s
跟改造他们有什么关系
helps reform them.
这不在于怎么射击 而在于教导他们什么是责任
Well, it's not about that. It teaches them responsibility.
至少这里给了他们一个机会
At least this place gives them a chance.
举枪
Port arms!
我能怎么协助你们
How can I be of assistance?
我知道Terrence Lewis
I understand Terrence Lewis
曾经在你的小队里 少校
was in your squad, Commander?
依然在我的小队里 是的
Is in my squad. Yes, sir.
不过 列兵Lewis近来...
Although, currently, Private Lewis is...
失踪了 我知道 你跟他熟吗
UA, I know. How well do you know him?
Walsh上将三个月前把他分配到我的小队里
General Walsh assigned him to my squad three months ago.
希望我能帮他改邪归正
Hoped I could straighten him out.
-怎么个情况 -能自由发言吗
- How so? - Permission to speak freely?
我们只是想寻找答案
We're just looking for answers.
只要有帮助 说什么都行
However you can help.
列兵Lewis是新兵中的刺头
Private Lewis was a difficult recruit.
这个学校
The academy prides itself
以忠诚和服从命令为荣
on strength through loyalty, following orders.
Lewis完全反着来
Lewis fought it every step of the way.
所以我可以理解为 你跟Lewis相处得并不好
So I take it you and Lewis didn't get along very well.
Lewis跟谁相处得都不好
Lewis didn't get along with anyone very well.
-那Noah律师呢 -律师
- What about JAG Noah? - JAG...
他是最好的 他一直在我们身边
He's the best, he's always been there for us.
他也帮Lewis 但是
Lewis, too, but...
但是什么 孩子
But what, son?
就在几周前 Noah律师想帮他
Just a few weeks ago, JAG Noah tried to help Lewis
从一些麻烦中脱身
with some stuff he was going through.
但是Lewis发了飚
But Lewis got mad.
变得更暴力
Violent, even.
还狠狠地打了Noah律师
Hit JAG Noah-- hard, too.
之后再也没人见过他
That's the last anyone ever saw of him.
那是什
What the...?
找到了
Bingo.
好的
Okay.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God!
根据腐烂程度
Judging by the rate of decomposition,
我推测这个男孩大概死于三周前
I'd estimate the boy died about three weeks ago.
跟Lewis失踪的时间一致
Same time Lewis went UA.
死因呢
Cause of death?
你这位失踪的学员
Your missing cadet
明显被打过
was obviously beaten.
即使过了这么久 他脸上
Even after all this time, bruises on his face,
胳膊上和胸口的伤痕依然明显
arms, and chest are still evident.
是啊 但更有意思的是 打他的凶器是什么
Yeah, more interesting, though, is what was used to beat him.
我们复原了
Yes, we recovered the same substance
表皮淤伤里发现的物质
found in the epidermis of the bruises--
碱液 甘油 氢氧化钾
lye, glycerin, potassium hydroxide...
也就是肥皂 我们甚至在他的嘴里发现了大量的肥皂痕迹
I.e., soap. We even found trace amounts of it in Lewis' mouth.
-肥皂 -肥皂打人
- Soap? - Soap bashing.
是军队一直谴责的一种欺凌方式
A hazing technique the military has long condemned.
只不过肥皂不能打断这个男孩的顶骨
Except soap didn't break the boy's parietal bone.
死因是后脑上
The cause of death was a sharp blow
致命的一击 我还在试着
to the back of the head, and I'm still trying
查清具体用的是什么凶器
to figure out exactly what was used.
欺凌过头了吗
Hazing gone too far?
如果是这样 Noah律师是把Lewis当成受害者
If so, JAG Noah may have been investigating
而不是少年犯来进行调查
Terrence Lewis as a victim, not a juvie.
不知怎么查出了弃尸地点
Somehow figured out where the body had been dumped,
前往Verre湖边调查
went to Lake Verret to investigate,
然后被杀害Lewis的人射杀了
and then got shot by whoever killed Lewis.
我真不想这么说 但是如果不止一个学员
Well, I hate to say it, but if more than one cadet
羞辱过Lewis 那很难相信
really did haze Lewis, then it's hard to believe
他们与两起谋杀案没有关联
they're not responsible for both murders.
我们不能直接下结论 好吗
We're not gonna jump to conclusions here, okay?
我们需要确认
We need to be sure.
好了 Loretta 我需要准确知道
Okay, Loretta, I need to know what exactly
杀害Terrence Lewis的凶器
was used to kill Terrence Lewis.
马上去
On it.
Sebastian
Sebastian,
查清杀害Noah律师的子弹
get an ID on those bullets
都是什么型号
that killed JAG Noah.
我想尽快知道
I want to know what type of weapon
它们来自哪种武器
they came from ASAP.
-收到 -你要去哪
- Copy that. - Where you going?
Rita刚发了信息
Rita just texted.
我得试着拖延她
I need to try and slow her down.
她一到就让她上来
Send her up as soon as she gets here.
Max Cabral 用致命武器袭击
Max Cabral, assault with a deadly weapon.
William Cole 暴力袭击
William Cole, aggravated assault.
-Jamal Povey 强奸未遂 -Rita
- Jamal Povey, attempted rape. - Rita...
Tyler Wilson 持枪抢劫 名单还没完呢
Tyler Wilson, armed robbery. And the list goes on.
在听到发生什么之后
I unsealed every cadet's criminal record
我解封了所有学员的犯罪记录
after I heard about what happened.
我知道Noah相信这些孩子 Dwayne
I know Noah believed in these boys, Dwayne.
我知道你也相信他们
I know you probably do, too.
但你不能说
But you can't tell me
他们都没有能力进行谋杀
none of them are capable of murder.
你不能因为他们的过去就对他们有偏见
You can't prejudge them from their past.
这不公平 这是改造的意义所在
That's not fair. That's what reform's all about.
这已经和改造无关了
This isn't about reform anymore.
这是关于正义
This is about justice.
我同意 但我想说的是
I agree, but all I'm saying is
我们知道的还不够
we don't know enough yet.
我们已经有足够的证据去申请
Well, we know enough to get a search and arrest warrant
对整个学校的搜索和逮捕令了
for the entire academy,
这正是我要去做的事情
which is exactly what I'm going to do.
但如果你错了呢
And what if you're wrong,
就像昨天
like you were yesterday,
你以为是Lewis杀了Noah
when you thought that Lewis killed Noah?
带着那些搜查令 媒体人员
Bring all those warrants, media follows,
让这件事情变成头条新闻
makes this headline news,
让Fort MacArthur关门大吉
and Fort MacArthur gets shut down.
-这是你想要的吗 -不 我想要正义
- Is that what you want? - No! I want justice,
你也应该想要正义
and you should want that, too.
-他们只是孩子 -他们是嫌疑犯
- They're boys. - They're suspects!
听着 我知道城里的人都爱戴你 Dwayne
Look, I know everybody in this town loves you, Dwayne.
他们一向如此 因为你总把他们放在第一位
They always have because you always put them first.
相信我 我知道
Believe me, I know.
这跟我们无关 Rita
This isn't about us, Rita.
我知道你是怎么长大的
I know how you grew up.
我知道你想要给所有人
I know how you want to give everyone,
尤其是那些弱者 无辜的推测
especially the underdogs, the benefit of the doubt,
但有时候他们不值得
but sometimes they don't deserve it.
我们还不知道
We don't know enough yet.
这对学校和那些孩子来说都太冒险了
There's too much risk to those boys and to the academy.
所以 Rita 拜托
So, Rita, please...
我不同意
I disagree.
Noah律师也许在你的执法范围内
JAG Noah may be your jurisdiction,
但Terrence Lewis归我管
but Terrence Lewis is mine.
我要去申请逮捕许可证
I'm getting the arrest warrants.
我不相信这些
I don't believe this.
凌辱 谋杀
Hazing? Murder?
如果这是真的 我已经失去了
If any of this is true, I've lost total control
对学校的控制
of this school.
你对此有多肯定
How certain are you of this?
杀死Noah的子弹可能来自于
The bullets that killed Noah could have come
学校的一把步枪
from one of the academy's rifles,
所以我们需要调查真相
so we need to find out what is true
看看我们是否能够控制局势
if we have any hopes of containing the situation.
因此 我们需要
And to do that, we need to
测试学员的步枪 进行匹配
test your cadets' rifles for matches,
还要知道哪个学生在两起谋杀发生的时候
and know which students were off-campus or on leave
不在学校 或者请假了
during both murders.
我去调记录
I'll get the logs.
安全
Clear!
谢谢大家的合作
Thank you guys for your cooperation.
在查清Noah律师的案子后
Didn't know how you would act
不知道你会作何反应
after finding out what happened to JAG Noah.
他会是第一个站出来安抚我们
He'd be the first to counsel calm
告诉我们服从命令
and tell us to follow orders,
这就是我在做的事情
and that's what I'm doing.
好了 下一个是谁的枪
Okay, whose rifle's up next?
-Cabral少校的 -拿来吧
- Commander Cabral's. - Let's have it.
我还是不明白 他们为什么检查我们的枪
I still don't understand, why are they checking our guns?
我不知道
I don't know.
Cabral少校 稍息
Commander Cabral. At ease.
Walsh上将要见你 少校
General Walsh needs to see you, Commander.
有关于士兵Lewis
It's about Private Lewis.
忠诚 荣誉 胜利
Fide, Honorem, Victoria.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
让队伍准备执行代号18
Prep the squad for Code 18.
-但是... -快去
- But... - Just do it!
- Christopher -怎么了
- Christopher? - What is it?
我不知道 但我有种不好的感觉
I don't know, but I don't have a good feeling about this.
这里一定有什么事情
Something's definitely up over there.
有个身份号在两起谋杀发生的时候都不在这里
One ID shows off premises at the time of both murders.
狗牌 2476
Dog tag 2476.
狗牌（身份牌），就是士兵的身份识别标志
247...
Max Cabral少校
Lieutenant Commander Max Cabral.
Max
Max?
是的 而且他的枪刚刚匹配上了
Yeah, well, his rifle just matched the bullets
杀死Noah律师的子弹
that killed JAG Noah.
这是什么
What's that?
是全面封锁
It's a lockdown.
但我没有下指令
But I didn't order it.
哇哦 这到底是什么情况
Whoa! What the hell is going on?
我在保护学校 举起手来
I'm protecting the academy. Hands up!
走吧 快点
Let's go, come on.
过来 快点 快走
Down here. Come on, let's go.
不要向后看
Stop looking back.
继续走 快点
Keep going, come on!
你不知道你在干什么 孩子
You don't know what you're doing, son.
你不在理智思考
You're not thinking straight.
-这到底是在... -坐下
- What is this supposed to... - Sit down!
坐下
Sit down!
-拿走他们的武器 -是 长官
- Pull their weapons. - Yes, sir.
你应该接这个电话 和他谈谈
You should answer that. Talk to him.
不 不要
No, don't.
不要
Don't.
我们在严格执行命令
We're under strict orders.
命令 谁给的命令
Orders? Orders from who?
看着他们
Stand watch.
走走走
Go! Go! Go!
-没接电话 -没有 好奇怪
- No answer? - No. It's weird.
-Pride -有消息吗
- Pride. - Anything?
新奥尔良警方和路易斯安那州州警正在疏散学生
NOPD and LSP are evacuating the students.
特别行动小组正在就位
SWAT's taking position.
天啊 Dorsey
Geez-- Dorsey!
为什么特别行动小组在这里
Why is SWAT here?
Rita
Rita.
她叫了他们 这是用于重罪逮捕令的程序
She called them. It's procedure when serving felony warrants,
看情况 显然是被准许了
and in this case, it's obviously warranted.
Christopher和Sonja在哪里
Where the hell are Christopher and Sonja?
警方看到一群人用枪指着他们
NOPD saw a squad of them take them
把他们带去了食堂
into the mess hall at gunpoint.
什么
What?
学生正在封锁窗户
Students were blocking the windows.
-没有人接电话 -这里的事态已经
- No one's answering. - Things are getting
失去控制了 将军 赶紧行动
out of hand here, General. Fast.
Dorsey
Dorsey!
长官
Sir.
你刚和Cabral少校说话 他说了什么
You just spoke to Commander Cabral, what did he say?
他没说什么 我就告诉他
Well, he didn't say anything. I just told him
你想要和他谈谈关于Lewis的事情
you wanted to talk to him about Lewis,
然后他就发起了全面封锁
then he triggered a lockdown.
你不觉得
You don't think Cabral
Cabral和这事情有关系吗
had anything to do with this, do you?
不不不 等等 我们现在知道的是
No, no, no. Hold on. All we know right now
子弹匹配了Cabral的枪
is that the bullets match Cabral's rifle.
-就这些 -对
- That's it. - Right.
他为什么会把他的枪交给我们呢
Why would he hand us over his rifle
当我们问他要的时候 他都没有犹豫
when we asked for it, without even hesitating,
如果他知道这会跟凶器匹配的话
if he knew it was gonna match the murder weapon?
他不会
He wouldn't have
-让你去测试 -去找Loretta
- let you test it. - Get ahold of Loretta.
好 希望她能给一些答案
Okay, let's hope she's got some answers.
我们错过了一些细节
We're missing something here.
我还在试着建立通信
I'm still trying to establish communication
等待无人机 原地待命
and waiting on drones, stand by.
地方检察官Devereaux 这是怎么回事 发生了什么
A.D.A. Devereaux. What's going on? What happened?
军校学员封锁了学校
The cadets have locked down the school.
等等 就因为逮捕令吗
Wait, because of the warrants?
我们还没能联系到他们
We never got a chance to serve them.
现在 他们隐藏起来 全副武装
Now, they're ensconced, heavily armed
他们有人质
and they've got hostages.
人质解救队多久能到
How long till HRT gets here?
15到20分钟
15 to 20 minutes,
但基于现在这种情况 我们等不了那么久
but based on the situation, we may not have that long.
我要在每扇窗和入口都安排狙击手
I want scopes in every window and access...
听着 我不想这事闹得这么大
Okay, look, I don't want this blowing up on us.
首先我们需要弄清楚他们想要什么
We need to find out what they want first.
这不是我决定的 而是取决于他们 但事实是
It's not up to me, it's up to them, but the fact is,
他们扣留了人质
is they've taken hostages.
嘿 他们会听我的
Hey, they'll listen to me.
让我进去 跟Cabral少校谈谈
Let me go in, talk to Commander Cabral.
我是他的指挥官 他会按我说的做
I'm his commanding officer, he'll do whatever I say.
这也许是救他们的唯一办法
It may be the only way to save them.
Terrence Lewis头上的致命击打伤
The lethal blow to the head on Terrence Lewis
是在凌辱之后发生的
was administered after the hazing.
之后多久
How long after?
12 15小时
12, 15 hours.
所以说 不是凌辱造成的
So, it's not due to the hazing?
除非Lewis事后威胁说要告诉别人
Unless Lewis threatened to tell somebody
然后就被杀了
after the fact, and got killed later.
好吧 这还不足以
Yeah, there's still not enough there
洗脱Cabral少校的嫌疑
to let Commander Cabral off the hook.
知道凶器是什么吗
Any idea what the murder weapon was?
不知道 但我确实发现了一些奇怪的细节
No, but I did find some curious details.
我在男孩的颅骨里
I found a sliver of wood
发现了一片木屑 不是普通的木头
in the boy's skull, not just any wood,
是200年树龄的西洋杉
but 200-year-old cedar.
还有微量的硫磺 炭 硝石
Also, trace amounts of sulfur, charcoal, saltpeter.
这听起来像是黑火药
That sounds like black gunpowder.
黑火药 你是说 可能源于内战时期
Black gunpowder, you mean, like from the Civil War?
是的
Yeah.
Pride 怎么了
Pride, what is it?
Sebastian
Sebastian,
如果有人使劲用这些旧的步枪击打
if somebody swung one of these old rifles hard enough,
微量的黑火药会...
could trace amounts of black gunpowder...
被晃出来 最终嵌入
Get dislodged, and end up embedded
颅骨吗 肯定会
in the skull? Absolutely.
上将 知不知道遗失的步枪在哪里
Any idea where the missing rifle is, General?
我从没注意到它丢了
I never even noticed it was gone.
还有谁有权进入这间办公室
Who else has access to the office?
Dorsey上校
Captain Dorsey.
Dorsey在哪里
Where is Dorsey?
这不是谈判
This is not a negotiation.
我们没有选择 上尉
We don't have a choice, Lieutenant.
我只是说 也许我们应该听他们的
All I'm saying is maybe we should listen to them.
我们没做错什么事
We didn't do anything wrong.
Lewis是因我们而死
Lewis is dead because of us!
我们是奉命去凌辱他
We were ordered to haze him,
就像现在我们也是在奉命行事
just like we were ordered to do this.
我们没有杀Lewis 更没有杀Noah律师
We didn't kill Lewis any more than we killed JAG Noah.
你认为外面的人会在乎这个吗
You think anyone outside of here cares about that?
这里所代表的一切都处于危险中
Everything this place stands for is on the line.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我们服从命令 就这样
We follow orders. Period.
但是最初 正是服从命令才让我们
But following orders is what got us into this mess
陷入这件事
in the first place.
Rita
Rita!
我很抱歉这么说 Dwayne 但我认为这证明了
I'm sorry to say this, Dwayne, but I think this proves
我对学员的看法是对的
I was right about the cadets.
事实上 我认为他们被陷害了
Actually, I think they're being set up.
我认为不是学员们杀了Lewis或者Noah
I don't think any of the cadets killed Lewis or Noah.
-证据呢 -你看到Dorsey上校了吗
- Based on what? - Have you seen Captain Dorsey?
Dorsey 我们刚让他进去 怎么了
Dorsey, we just sent him inside. Why?
原地候命
Stand down.
你本该控制住局面的 学员
You were supposed to contain the situation, Cadet.
现在我得来收拾摊子
Now I have to clean it up.
跟我来
With me.
我想说的是 情况可能不像看起来那样
All I'm saying is, the situation may not be as it appears.
我们认为Cabral少校
We think Commander Cabral's
被你们刚放进去的人陷害了
being set up by the man you just let inside.
Cabral扣留了两名你的人当人质
Cabral is holding two of your own people hostage.
他只是在服从命令
He's just following orders.
我也一样 我的工作是清除危险 Pride探员
And so am I. My job is clear, Agent Pride,
就是要尽我所能去缓和局势
and that's to defuse the situation any way I can.
-Dugan -失陪
- Dugan? - Excuse me.
这说不通
This doesn't make any sense.
如果你是对的 那些男孩是无罪的
If you're right, and the boys are innocent,
为什么要这么做 为什么要扣留人质
why do this? Why take hostages?
整个改造的前提是教会学员们
The whole premise of reform here is to teach cadets
绝对服从命令
to obey orders without question,
把军校放在第一位
to put the academy first.
显然 Dorsey利用了这点
Obviously, Dorsey took advantage of that.
等等 你是说Dorsey杀了Noah和Lewis 为什么
Wait, you're saying Dorsey killed Noah and, and Lewis? Why?
-Pride -跟我说说情况
- Pride. - Talk to me.
上将让我查阅了Dorsey的人事档案
The general got me access to Dorsey's personnel files.
看样子 在上一位上将死后
Apparently, he applied to take over the academy
他申请了接管学校 但是却由Walsh接管了
after the last general died, but Walsh got it instead.
-这不是谋杀的动机 -是的
- That's not motivation for murder. - Well, no.
但他被否决的主要原因却可能成为动机
But the main reason that he got passed over might be.
Dorsey曾多次因滥用职权
See, Dorsey had been reprimanded several times
而被谴责
for abuse of authority,
包括下达凌辱学员的命令
including ordering the hazing of cadets.
所以Lewis这事做得过火了
So things with Lewis went too far,
不受他们失控了 Noah律师发现了
they got out of hand, JAG Noah figured it out...
他不得不也杀了他
And he had to kill him, too.
还是解释不了为什么Cabral
Still doesn't explain why Cabral
封锁了学校
locked down the school.
不 可以解释
No, it does.
这能说通 如果他是奉了Dorsey的命令
It does, if he's following Dorsey's orders.
而Dorsey想让Max看起来有罪...
And if Dorsey's trying to make Max look guilty...
Gregorio在哪里
Where's Gregorio?
我们只有一次机会
We only got one shot at this.
收到 Pride 我只希望我们有足够的时间
Got it, Pride. I just hope we have enough time.
嘿 如果你是无罪的
Hey. If you're innocent,
如果Max是无罪的 我们可以证明
if Max is innocent, we can prove it,
但不是这样
But not like this.
除此之外 就连军队都会不遵守命令
Besides, even the military's not supposed to follow orders
如果命令是不合法的
if they're illegal,
或者犯法的 嘿 你也一样
or criminal... hey, and neither are you.
如果你想做正确的事
Look, if you want to do what's right?
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
我们可以趁早停止这些
We can stop this before it's too late.
你能阻止
You can stop this.
但请你
But please,
让我们走
let us go.
你是军队的耻辱
You are an embarrassment to the uniform.
这是你的烂摊子 少校
This is your mess, Commander.
我是服从你的命令
I was following your orders.
我的命令是保护学校
My orders were to protect the academy,
不是把它置于险境
not to put it at risk,
而那却是你所做的
which is exactly what you've done.
你到底在想什么
What the hell were you thinking?
你是开始这一切的人
You're the one that started this.
是你让我凌辱Lewis 吓吓他
You're the one that told me to haze Lewis, scare him straight.
但你做过头了 不是吗
But you went too far, didn't you?
Lewis威胁说要把事情抖出来
Lewis threatened to expose it,
但那就破坏了学校的制度
but that would've brought down the very institution
你就要在监狱里
that's kept you from spending the rest
度过你可怜的余生
of your sorry-ass life in prison.
我没有杀Lewis
I didn't kill Lewis!
但我不得不
But I had to!
为了保护学校
To protect the academy
免受同样的混乱
from the same mess.
那Noah律师呢
What about JAG Noah?
也算你头上
Also on you.
在他弄明白发生了什么之后
After he figured out what happened,
找到了Lewis的尸体
tracked down Lewis's body,
我必须做点什么 来保护我们免遭你的连累
I had to do something to protect us all from your screwups!
忠诚高于一切
Loyalty above all else!
记得吗
Remember that?
那是这个地方所代表的意义
That's what this place stands for.
但显然你没有做到
But that's something you obviously don't get.
你是个失败者 Cabral
You're a failure, Cabral,
对你自己 对学校 都是失败者
a failure to yourself, and this institution.
你应该为你自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself!
我可以开火吗
Do I have permission to fire?
你以为你控制了一切吗
You think you got the balls?
来啊 开枪啊 朝我开枪
Go ahead, pull the trigger! Shoot me!
不行 但我可以 挪开
No, but I do. Move.
来啊
Do it!
联邦探员 不许动
Federal agents! Don't move!
举起手来
Put your hands up!
警报解除 警报解除
All clear, all clear.
漂亮的一枪 Gregorio
Nice shot, Gregorio.
我知道你可以做到
I knew you could do it.
等你下来了再见
See you when you get back down here.
收到
Copy that.
只是出于好奇
Just out of curiosity,
你怎么知道那个计划可行
how'd you know that would work?
那是Dorsey的计划吗
That that was Dorsey's plan?
我不知道 我不清楚
I didn't, but I couldn't figure out
他还会做什么
what else he was gonna do.
穷途末路 知道我们要逮捕他
Backed in the corner, knew we were onto him,
假设事态会升级
assumed things would escalate.
所以 换句话说 这只是直觉吗
So, in other words, it was just a hunch?
我更乐意说是"有依据的推测"
I prefer “educated guess.”
还是不能完全了解他
Still can't quite figure him out.
了解谁 Pride吗
Figure out who? Pride?
-对 -他有什么好了解的
- Yeah. - What's there to figure out?
他就是那种人啊
He's the man.
我想她说的是他的私生活
I think she's talking about his personal life.
哦
Oh.
弹钢琴是他的私生活
Yeah, but playing piano is his personal life.
不 还有比这个更私密的事情
Nah, there's got to be more to it than that.
他这么优质的男人
He's such a good catch.
他不应该被人勾搭吗 不是吗
I mean, he should be hooked up with someone, no?
把话说清楚 现在聊的只是出于职业好奇
Talking professional curiosity here, let's just be clear.
King并不急着
Look, King is not in a hurry to get together
找个人在一起
with anyone anytime soon.
他喜欢当King
He's just happy being King.
没错 好吧 像我刚刚说的
It's true. Okay. Well, like I said,
他是个优质男 只是不大符合常理罢了
he's a great catch, and it's just not natural.
你只是因为输掉了关于Rita的打赌而不爽
You're just cranky that you lost the bet about Rita.
-对了 -没错 我都忘了
- Bingo. - Exactly! I forgot.
我有不爽吗
I'm cranky? I'm cranky?
-对 你有 -那她为什么来了
- Yeah, you cranky. - Then why is she here?
啊哈
Huh?
看来你还记得我的话
I see I made an impression on you.
是吗 弹的怎么样
Oh, yeah? How's that?
轻敲琴键 没那么紧绷了
Lighter touch on the keys, less tense.
好吧 你非常有自信
All right, you're pretty confident.
还好啦
Uh, not so much.
在我差点酿成惨剧之后 就没那么自信了
Certainly not after I nearly caused a disaster.
你太苛责你自己了
You're being too hard on yourself.
还有什么新鲜的
Eh. What else is new?
我早该知道
I should've known better.
我应该记住的
I should've remembered.
永远不要和你的直觉过不去
Never go up against one of your hunches.
我不知道 我的方法也有跑偏的时候
Oh, I don't know, my way could've gone sideways, too.
鉴于那些孩子在上军校前
Troubled history those kids had even before
问题重重的历史 很难不想到
they get to the academy, hard not to think
无风不起浪
that where there's smoke, there's fire.
这就是Dorsey上校希望
Well, certainly what Captain Dorsey was hoping
让大家相信的事情
to make everybody believe.
地方检察署认为他不仅试图陷害Max
D.A. thinks he wasn't just trying to frame Max,
还想让Walsh难看 这样他就能接管学校
but also make Walsh look bad so he could take over.
可是却差点搞垮了学校
Almost brought down the academy instead.
谢谢为他们的行为说了好话
Thanks for putting in a good word on their behalf.
这是我最起码能做的事情了
Oh, it's the least I could do.
毕竟 那些孩子值得拥有第二次机会
After all, those boys deserve a second chance.
没错 我同意
Yeah, I agree with that.
继续说
Yeah, go ahead.
对了
By the way...
记得这个吗
Remember this one?
别 拜托 别弹那个
No-- don't. Please, don't go there.
怎么 你害怕了
What, are you scared?
歌名《It had to be you》(那必须是你)
那必须是你
♪ It had to be you ♪
调子错了
Uh, wrong key, though.
什么
What?
我四处漫步
♪ I wandered around ♪
终于找到了那个人
♪ Finally found somebody who... ♪
很不错啊
That's perfect.
没 太低了
No, it's too low.
他让我真实
♪ Could make me be true ♪
他让我难过
♪ Could make me be blue ♪
即使很高兴
♪ Or even be glad ♪
一想到你还是难过
♪ Just to be sad thinking of you ♪
我见过的其他人
♪ Some others I've seen ♪
-就是这样 -好的
- There it is. - Okay.
可能并不平庸
♪ Might never be mean ♪
你可能是对的
May be right.
可能并不易怒
♪ Might never be cross ♪
也不会强势
♪ Or try to be boss ♪
他们不会
♪ They wouldn't do ♪
因为没有人
♪ For nobody else ♪
给钱
Pay up.
来吧
Let's go.
有你全部的缺点
♪ With all your faults ♪
我却依然爱你
♪ I love you still ♪
谢啦
Thank you.
那必须是你
♪ It had to be you ♪
不能刷卡真是亏了
Too bad you don't take credit.
那必须是你
♪ It had to be you. ♪